The Thomas and Ryan families
Marist Archives and Special Collections
The Thomas and Ryan families
2.3.3.1
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1621
- The Thomas and Ryan families, 2.3.3.1
  - Unframed, round photograph mounted on metal of a small girl with bows in her hair, late 1800s - early 1900s; 1-2; 6 x 6 color (Box 1621)
  - Unframed, round photograph mounted on metal of a young child, late 1800s - early 1900s; 3; 6 x 6 color (Box 1621)
  - Unframed, round photograph mounted on metal of a middle aged woman, late 1800s - early 1900s; 4; 6 x 6 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Posed photograph of a young girl, undated; 5; 9½ x 13½ b&w (Box 1621)
  - Andrew Calvin McCorkle [Frances Ryan Thomas’s grandfather], undated; 6; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Emeline McCorkle [Frances Ryan Thomas’s grandmother] [photograph], undated; 7; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Mary Eunice McCorkle Ryan [Frances Ryan Thomas’s mother] [photograph], undated; 8; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Norman Ryan [Frances Ryan Thomas’s brother] [photograph], undated; 9; 11 x 16 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Harry G. Thomas, Harriet Wagner Thomas and Lowell Thomas [photograph], circa 1894; 10; 11½ x 14 sepia (Box 1621)
  - Harriet Wagner Thomas and Lowell Thomas [photograph], 1897; 11-12; 11 x 14½ b&w (Box 1621)
  - Family photograph; Harriet Wagner Thomas and Harry G. Thomas at left, Lowell Thomas standing third from right, 1907 - 1908; 13; 10 x 12 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Family photograph; Harriet Wagner Thomas and Harry G. Thomas at left, Lowell Thomas standing third from right; verso: Wagner reunion in Darke County, Ohio, near Greenville in 1908. At home of L.T.’s mother’s oldest sister, Mrs. Sanford Vantilborg [duplicate of item 13], 1907 - 1908; 14; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Family photograph; Harriet Wagner Thomas and Harry G. Thomas at left, Lowell Thomas standing third from right; verso: summer 1907, age 15, mother’s family, Greenville, Ohio [duplicate of item 13], 1907 - 1908; 15; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Harry G. Thomas [photograph], 1901 - 1902; 16-17; 11½ x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Harry G. Thomas; caption: On top of Pikes Peak All 14147 ft. Sunday July 20, 1902 [photograph], 18-19; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Harry G. Thomas in his medical office in Victor, Colorado; verso: Dr. H. G. Thomas - 1914 shortly before he left Victor for World War I [photograph], 20-21; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Harry G. Thomas posed photograph, circa 1930s; 22; 8 x 10 hand-colored (Box 1621)
  - Lowell Thomas and his sister Pherbia Thomas [Thornburg]; verso: in 1911 - After a short period in mines [Lowell Thomas] becomes editor of Victor Daily Record, and in 1912 editor of new paper, Victor Daily News [photograph], 23-24; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. on horseback [photograph], circa 1930; 25; 10 x 12 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. holding snowshoes [photograph], circa early 1930s; 26; 10 x 12 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Lowell Thomas, Jr. pulling boot off unidentified man; Frances Ryan Thomas in background [photograph], circa late 1930s; 27; 10 x 12 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. with family dogs [photograph], circa late 1930s; 28-29; 10 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. in uniform [photograph], circa 1940; 30-31; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas, circa 1940s; 32; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas stand before WFIL radio microphone [photograph], circa 1940s; 33-34; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. in uniform [photograph], circa 1940; 35; 10 x 12 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. holding map while posing before picture of the Potala [photograph], circa 1950s; 36-37; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Posed photograph of Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. in profile, circa 1950s; 38-43; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1621)
  - Lowell Thomas and his granddaughter Anne Thomas [photograph], circa 1960s; 44; 11 x 14 color (Box 1621)
  - Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, Lowell and Tay Thomas, Jr. and their children David and Anne [photograph], circa 1960s; 45; 16 x 20 color (Box 1621)
  - Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, Lowell and Tay Thomas, Jr. and their children David and Anne [photograph], circa 1960s; 46-47; 16 x 20 color (Box 1621)
  Box 1622
- The Thomas and Ryan families, 2.3.3.1
  - Herbert Mitchell portrait: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. [framed photograph], circa 1930; 1; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1622)
  - Herbert Mitchell portrait: Frances Ryan Thomas [framed photograph], circa 1930; 2; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1622)
  - Herbert Mitchell portrait: Lowell Thomas, Jr. [framed photograph], circa 1930; 3; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1622)
  - Herbert Mitchell portrait: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. [same as item 1] [unframed photograph], circa 1930; 4; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1622)
  - Herbert Mitchell portrait: Frances Ryan Thomas [same as item 2] [unframed photograph], circa 1930; 5; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1622)
  - Herbert Mitchell portrait: Frances Ryan Thomas [photograph], circa 1930; 6; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1622)
  - Herbert Mitchell portrait: Frances Ryan Thomas [photograph], circa 1930; 7; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1622)
  - Herbert Mitchell portrait: Lowell Thomas, Jr. [same as item 3] [unframed photograph], circa 1930; 8; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1622)
  - Herbert Mitchell portrait: Lowell Thomas, Jr. [photograph], circa 1930; 9; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1622)
  - Herbert Mitchell portrait: Lowell Thomas, Jr. [photograph], circa 1930; 10; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1622)
  - Herbert Mitchell portrait: Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. [photograph], circa 1930; 11; 11 x 14 b&w (Box 1622)
  - Herbert Mitchell portrait: Frances Ryan Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr. [photograph], circa 1930; 12; 12½ x 16½ b&w (Box 1622)